Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1947-1988; 1970-1985; 7; 11 cubic ft.
  - General Secretary's Report for 1965 [RESTRICTED] (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1966 [RESTRICTED] (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1967 [RESTRICTED] (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1970 [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - General Secretary's Report for 1971 [RESTRICTED] (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - "Georgia Residents' Attitudes Toward the Death Penalty, the Disposition of Juvenile Offenders and Related Issues" [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Gideon Decision (Study of Recidivism and Socio - cultural Change) [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Governmental Attitude and Action toward Prostitution [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Governor's Special Committee on Criminal Offenders, Observations on Preliminary Report of [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force on Alcoholism Treatment in Criminal Justice - Report [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Green, William - Resume [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Greyhound [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - GRI - Governmental Research Institute [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - GROW - Group Relations Ongoing Workshops [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Guidelines on the Use of Arrest and Conviction Records as Job Selection Criteria [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Gun Control [RESTRICTED], 1980-1985 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Half-Way Houses [RESTRICTED], 1963-1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Harris, M. Kay - Articles [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Heroin Use in a Provincial Town - One Year Later [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Herstedvester Detention Center (Netherlands) [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Hoffa, James - Testimony [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Home Detention [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Homicide [RESTRICTED], 1968-1969 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Homicide in New York State [RESTRICTED], 1981; 1983 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Homosexuality [RESTRICTED], 1969-1973 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Human Resources Administration Services, Commissioner's Statement on [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Human Services Management Institute, Inc. [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - ICC Link [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Illegal Aliens - Incarceration [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Incarceration - Cost Effectiveness [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Incarceration Costs [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Inmate Population Distribution [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Inmate Problems, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Inquiry into the Juvenile Centers Operated by the Office of Probation [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Interfaith Coalition for Equal Justice [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - "Inside America's Toughest Prison" [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - International Council on Alcohol and Addictions [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Is the Alcoholic Immune from Criminal Prosecution [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Jails [RESTRICTED], 1965-1969 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Jail Reform - National Coalition [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Jailing the Drunken Alcoholic - It's "Cruel and Unusual Punishment" [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Jails/Jail Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Jails - Population Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Jaycees [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Job Problems of Ex-offenders [RESTRICTED], 1969-1976; 2 folders (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45-46)
  - Job Training [RESTRICTED], 1967-1973 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Judges on Prisons [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Judicial Conference [RESTRICTED], 1967-1971 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Judicial Selection [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - Justifiable Abortions [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - Juvenile Courts [RESTRICTED], 1962-1967 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - Juvenile Delinquency [RESTRICTED], 1964-1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - Juvenile Detention Association, National [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - Juvenile Detention Centers [RESTRICTED], 1968-1972 (Box 4 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
  - Juvenile Detention Panel [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1-2)
  - Juveniles [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Juveniles [RESTRICTED], 1973-1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Juveniles [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Juveniles and Juvenile Justice System [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Lasker Decision - House of Detention for Men [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Lasker Decision - House of Detention for Men [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Law and Disorder [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Legal Aid Society [RESTRICTED], 1968-1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Legal Aid Society [RESTRICTED], 1968-1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Legal Issues of Female Inmates: A Report [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Legal Situation on Jailing Alcoholics for Public Intoxication in the United States [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Legal Status of Alcoholics - Social Welfare Implications [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Legislation - NYS: 1973 Session [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Liman Commission [RESTRICTED], 1982; 2 folders (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16-17)
  - Long Island Correctional Facility - Closure [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Man on the Periphery [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Mandatory Sentences in Drug Cases [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Marijuana [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Marshaling Citizen Power to Modernize Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts [RESTRICTED], 1980-1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Media [RESTRICTED], 1980-1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Methadone Program [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Minimum Standards of Civil and Human Rights for Inmates in Correctional Institutions [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Minnesota [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Minnesota Community Corrections Act Evaluation [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1981-1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Model Residential Juvenile Sex-offender Treatment Program [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Moratorium Advocates [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Narcotic Addiction [RESTRICTED], 1964-1966 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Narcotic Addiction - Confronting the Realities [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Nassau County Correctional Center [RESTRICTED], 1972-1983 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - National Conference on Correctional Policy [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - National Conference on Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - National Council of Churches [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency [RESTRICTED], 1962-1982 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - National Institute of Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - National Institute of Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - National Institute for Sentencing Alternatives [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 5 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - National Jail Association [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - National Moratorium on Prison Construction [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - National Organizations [RESTRICTED], 1982-1987 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - National Prison Project [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - National Prisoner Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1961-1975 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - National Prisoner Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - New Jersey [RESTRICTED], ca. 1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Association on Correction [RESTRICTED], 1974-1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - New Jersey Association on Correction, News and Views [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Corrections Quarterly [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - New York City - Alternative Programs [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - New York City Bar Association [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - New York City Bar Association - Council on Criminal Justice [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - New York City Board of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1977-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - New York City Board of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - New York City - Budget [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - New York City - Budget [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - New York City - Budget [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - New York City - Budget - Message of the Mayor [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - New York City - Budget Summary - Fiscal Year 1985 [RESTRICTED] (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - New York City - Capital Costs [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - New York City - Citizens' Budget Commission [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - New York City - Correctional Costs [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - New York City - Costs [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - New York City - Courts [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - New York City - Crime and Corrections [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - New York City - Crime Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - New York City - Criminal Justice System [RESTRICTED], 1977-1987 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - New York City Department of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1971-1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - New York City Department of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1979-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - New York City Department of Correction - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32-33)
  - New York City Department of Correction - Rehabilitation Services Coordinating Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - New York City - Impact of President Reagan's Proposed Budget [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - New York City - Jail Expansion [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding, Lynch Committee on [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - New York City - Jail Overcrowding, Lynch Committee on [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - New York City - Jails - Forced Release [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - New York City - Jails - 1986 Crisis [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - New York City - Jails - 1986 Crisis - Court Papers [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - New York City - Job Programs for Youths [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - New York City Office of Budget and Management [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - New York City - Prison Programs Resources [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - New York City - Police [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - New York City - Probation [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - New York City - Report - Pretrial Services [RESTRICTED], ca. 1975-1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - New York City - Testimony [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - New York City - Youth Programs [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 6 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - New York Coalition for Penal Reform [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - New York Family Planner [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration - Estimated Costs and Savings [RESTRICTED], ca. 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration Task Force [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - New York State - Alternatives to Incarceration Task Force - Report [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - New York State Assembly - Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force Conference [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - New York State - Bail [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - New York State Bar Association - "BASIC" Grants [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - New York State Bar Visitation Project [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - New York State - Budget - Corrections, Alternatives [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - New York State - Budget - General [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - New York State Catholic Conference [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - New York State Coalition for Criminal Justice [RESTRICTED], 1975-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - New York State Commission of Correction-Site Visits [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - New York State Commission of Investigation, Annual Report [RESTRICTED], 1985; 1985-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - New York State - Crime Rates [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - New York State Communities' Aid Association [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - New York State - County Jails [RESTRICTED], 1981-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - New York State - Cuomo, Mario [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - New York State Defenders Association Brochure [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services [RESTRICTED], 1975-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Fiscal Year 1988-89 [RESTRICTED] (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - New York State Department of Correctional Services - Division of Program Planning - Research and Evaluation - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - New York State Developmental Disabilities Planning Council [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - New York State Division for Youth Assistance Project [RESTRICTED], 1964-1974 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - New York State Division of Parole - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1980-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - New York State Division of Probation - Sentencing Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - New York State Division of Probation - Sentencing Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - New York State - Governor's State of the State Address - Criminal Justice Section [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - New York State - Gubernatorial Candidates [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - New York State Law Enforcement Council [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - New York State Law Enforcement Council [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - New York State - Laws and Evaluations [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - New York State - Legislation - Mandatory Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - New York State - Legislation - Prison Overcrowding [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - New York State - Legislative Breakfast [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - New York State - Legislative History - 1973 Amendment [RESTRICTED] (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - New York State - Legislative Memoranda - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - New York State Legislature - Black and Puerto Rican Caucus [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - New York State - Mental Hygiene Law Summary [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - New York State Narcotic Addiction control Commission [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - New York State Office of Mental Health - Forensic Unit [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - New York State Office of Vocational Rehabilitation [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - New York State Prisons, Classification of [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - New York State Prisons - Expansion Programs - Overcrowding [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - New York State Prisons - Rehabilitation Programs [RESTRICTED], 1973-1985 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - New York State Prisons - Sex Offenders [RESTRICTED], 1983-1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - New York State Probation and Parole Officers Association, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - New York State - Parole Board [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - New York State - Reform Groups [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines Committee [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
  - Neufeld, Muriel [RESTRICTED], ca. 1985 (Box 7 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 56)
  - News Bulletin, June and October 1984 [RESTRICTED] (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - News Bulletin [RESTRICTED], 1986 December 19 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings - Op-ed - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings - Op-ed - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - News Update, Summer 1983 [RESTRICTED] (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - 1960 Golden Anniversary White House Conference on Children and Youth [RESTRICTED] (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - On the City's Master Plan - Summary [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)